Guide to the Richard Minsky Archive
Yale University Arts Library
- Project Files, 1968-2010; Series IV
  - IBM, undated (Box 38, Folder 90)
  - Miscellaneous Works, undated (Box 38, Folder 91)
    See also: Oversize, box 47, folder 136; Oversize, box 47, folder 138; Oversize, box 48, folder 144; Oversize, box 49, folder 145; Oversize, box 50, folder 148.
  - Miscellaneous Works, undated (Box 39, Folder 92)
  - Naturgeschichte der Amphibien, undated (Box 39, Folder 93)
  - Private Commissions
    - Kertesz Portfolio Box, 1981-1985 (Box 39, Folder 94)
    - Gracie Mansion Register, 1984-1985 (Box 39, Folder 95)
      See also: Oversize, box 50, folder 147; Oversize, box 50, folder 148.
    - Long Island Guest Book, 1986 (Box 39, Folder 96)
    - Cohen Wedding, 1987-1989 (Box 39, Folder 97)
    - Cohen Wedding, 1987-1989 (Box 39, Folder 98)
      - Correspondence, 1987-1989 (Box 39, Folder 99)
    - Brooklyn Museum Director's Guest Book, 1989 (Box 39, Folder 100)
      See also: Oversize, Bsd, folder 150.
      - Stamping Plates, 1989 (Box 40, Folder 101)
    - Orenstein Sundial Sculpture, 1992 (Box 40, Folder 102)
      - Correspondence, 1992 (Box 40, Folder 103)
    - Warner Music Group, 1994 (Box 40, Folder 104)
      - Correspondence, 1994-1995 (Box 40, Folder 105)
      - Stamping Dies, 1994 (Box 40, Folder 106)
    - Gutfreund Dictionary/Thesaurus Set, 1994 (Box 40, Folder 107)
      - Correspondence, 1994 (Box 40, Folder 108)
    - Chateau Vervaines Guestbook, 1994 (Box 40, Folder 109)
      - Correspondence, 1993-94 (Box 40, Folder 110)
      - Mold, 1994 (Box 40, Folder 111)
    - Chateau Vervaines Paintings, 1996 (Box 40, Folder 112)
    - Tribute to Ronald Lauder – Stamping Die, 1997 (Box 40, Folder 113)
    - A Celebration of Life (Collins), 2001 (Box 40, Folder 114)
    - A Celebration of Life (Collins), 2001 (Box 41, Folder 115)
    - A Celebration of Life (Lipari), 2001 (Box 41, Folder 116)
    - A Celebration of Life (Lipari), 2001 (Box 41, Folder 117)
    - Dave Walsh/Scholastic Book, 2001 (Box 41, Folder 118)
    - Dave Walsh/Scholastic Book, 2001 (Box 41, Folder 119)
    - The Big Game Trophy Rooms of Huck Spaulding: Stamping Die, 2001-2002 (Box 41, Folder 120)
    - Grosbard Bar Mitzvah, 2004 (Box 41, Folder 121)
      - Mold, 2004 (Box 41, Folder 122)
      - Cast Hardware, 2004 (Box 42, Folder 123)
    - Bernie Cantor Card, undated (Box 42, Folder 124)
    - Louis Meisel, undated (Box 42, Folder 125)
    - Stux Family Album, undated (Box 42, Folder 126)
- Interviews with Richard Minsky, 2014; Series V
  The series consists of short interviews with Minsky about specific items in the archive. Each interview sheds light on Minsky's creative process and situates the artifacts in the archive into the picture of his career. Recounted with Minsky's characteristic humor, the interviews are entertaining as well as educational.
  Audio files are arranged in the box and folder order where the items under discussion are located.
  - AOB 8 Box 2 Folder 10-1, 2014-07; 1 computer file (MP4); 3 minutes and 6 seconds
  - AOB 8 Box 3 Folder 15-1, 2014-07; 1 computer file (MP4); 2 minutes and 24 seconds
  - AOB 8 Box 3 Folder 16-1, 2014-07; 1 computer file (MP4); 4 minutes and 57 seconds
  - AOB 8 Box 3 Folder 16-2, 2014-07; 1 computer file (MP4); 1 minute and 9 seconds
  - AOB 8 Box 3 Folder 16-3, 2014-07; 1 computer file (MP4); 1 minute and 44 seconds
  - AOB 8 Box 4 Folder 19-1, 2014-07; 1 computer file (MP4); 3 minutes and 19 seconds
  - AOB 8 Box 12 Folder 61-1, 2014-07; 1 computer file (MP4); 2 minutes and 48 seconds
  - AOB 8 Box 12 Folder 61-2, 2014-07; 1 computer file (MP4); 2 minutes and 15 seconds
  - AOB 8 Box 12 Folder 62-1, 2014-07; 1 computer file (MP4); 1 minute and 19 seconds
  - AOB 8 Box 13 Folder 68-1, 2014-07; 1 computer file (MP4); 2 minutes and 38 seconds
  - AOB 8 Box 18 Folder 96-1, 2014-07; 1 computer file (MP4); 2 minutes and 29 seconds
  - AOB 8 Box 23 Folder 118-1, 2014-07; 1 computer file (MP4); 2 minutes and 17 seconds
  - AOB 8 Box 23 Folder 119-1, 2014-07; 1 computer file (MP4); 1 minute and 7 seconds
  - AOB 8 Box 24 Folder 129-1, 2014-07; 1 computer file (MP4); 2 minutes and 56 seconds
  - AOB 8 Box 29 Folder 155-1, 2014-07; 1 computer file (MP4); 3 minutes and 7 seconds
  - AOB 8 Box 34-1, 2014-07; 1 computer file (MP4); 3 minutes and 10 seconds
  - AOB 8 Box 34 Folder 41-1, 2014-07; 1 computer file (MP4); 2 minutes and 33 seconds
  - AOB 8 Box 34 Folder 42-1, 2014-07; 1 computer file (MP4); 48 seconds
  - AOB 8 Box 34 Folder 42-2, 2014-07; 1 computer file (MP4); 2 minutes and 40 seconds
  - AOB 8 Box 43 Folder 127-1, 2014-07; 1 computer file (MP4); 2 minutes and 58 seconds
  - AOB 8 Box 43 Folder 129-1, 2014-07; 1 computer file (MP4); 2 minutes and 5 seconds
  - AOB 8 Box 61-1, 2014-07; 1 computer file (MP4); 1 minute and 50 seconds
- Oversize, 1968-2010
  - From Series IV: Project Files, 1980-2002
    - Bill of Rights Amendment I (Box 43, Folder 127)
    - Bill of Rights Proposal Board (Box 43, Folder 127)
      See also Series V for Minsky's discussion of the cover design for The First Amendment in the Bill of Rights series.
    - Paper & Canvas Tests for Bill of Rights Series (Box 43, Folder 128)
    - Pistol Targets for Bill of Rights (Box 43, Folder 129)
      See also Series V for Minsky's discussion of the pistol targets for the Bill of Rights series.
    - Layout for Class of '47 invite (Box 43, Folder 129)
    - Layout for Minsky in London backpages (Box 43, Folder 129)
  - From Series III: Business Files & Correspondence, 1992 undated
    - Richard Minsky Catalog (Box 43, Folder 130)
    - Business Signage (Box 43, Folder 130)
    - Tom Martin Show Serigraph Poster (Box 43, Folder 130)
  - From Series I: Biographical, 1969 1989-2005
    - New York Daily News - "Men Walk on the Moon" (Box 43, Folder 131)
    - New York Times – "Men Walk on Moon" (Box 43, Folder 131)
    - Bill of Rights ArtNews Ad (Box 43, Folder 131)
    - Review of Bill of Rights (Box 43, Folder 132)
    - Dan's Papers Article (Box 43, Folder 132)
    - Dan's Papers Article (Box 43, Folder 132)
    - Dan's Papers Article (Box 43, Folder 132)
    - The Paper Article (Box 43, Folder 132)
  - From Series IV: Project Files, 1980
    - Minsky in London (Box 43, Folder 133)
  - From Series I: Biographical, 1979-2008 undated
    - Sheet Music – Two Duets By Mozart (Box 43, Folder 134)
    - "The Artist & the Book Today", 1979 (Box 43, Folder 134)
    - "The Artist & London College of Printing", 1979 (Box 47, Folder 135)
    - "The Artist & Camberwell School of Art & Crafts", 1979 (Box 47, Folder 135)
    - Are Books A Burning Issue?, 1980 (Box 47, Folder 135)
    - University of the Arts, 2008 (Box 47, Folder 135)
  - From Series IV: Project Files, 1970-2000 undated
    - Les Fleurs du Mal, ca. 1960-1970 (Box 47, Folder 136)
    - The Ethics of Visual Art… (Box 47, Folder 136)
    - The Eye Sees Light…, 1994 (Box 47, Folder 136)
    - Misc. Works (Box 47, Folder 136)
    - Prométhée, ca. 1960-1970 (Box 47, Folder 136)
    - Blank Book for Dante's Inferno, 1979 (Box 47, Folder 136)
    - Study for Box for Go, ca. 1970 (Box 47, Folder 137)
    - Minsky in Bed, 1989-1996 (Box 47, Folder 137)
    - Dreaming the Caves, 1991 (Box 47, Folder 138)
    - Chateau Vervaines Guestbook, 1994 (Box 47, Folder 138)
    - Animal Magnetism, 1992-1993 (Box 47, Folder 138)
    - The First Time I Thought About Suicide But Didn't, 1991 (Box 47, Folder 138)
    - Branches Posters, 2000 (Box 47, Folder 138)
  - From Series I: Biographical, 1979-1985 undated
    - Book Architecture, 1985 (Box 47, Folder 139)
    - Book Makers, 1979 (Box 47, Folder 139)
    - Center for Book Arts (Box 47, Folder 139)
  - From Series IV: Project Files, 1989-1996 2006-2010 undated
    - Minsky in Bed (Box 46, Folder 140)
    - Minsky in Bed (Box 46, Folder 141)
    - American Decorated Publisher's Bindings, 1872-1929, vol. 1 proofs, 2006 (Box 47, Folder 142)
    - American Decorated Publisher's Bindings, 1872-1929, vol. 1, 2006 (Box 47, Folder 143)
    - Art of American Book Covers vol. 3, 2010 (Box 47, Folder 143)
    - Misc. Works (Box 48)
      Includes The Book Art of Richard Minsky cover draft.
  - From Series I: Biographical, circa 1990 undated
    - Photo of Minsky at 15 Bleecker Street (Box 48, Folder 144)
    - Photo of Minsky, Roger Haile, Pat Gorman, Barbara Slate, Nick Caraccio, Lulu Bagnall, Joni Mabe (Box 48, Folder 144)
  - From Series IV: Project Files, 1973 1980 1985 1998 undated
    - Misc. Works (Box 49, Folder 145)
    - Minsky in London (Box 49, Folder 146)
    - Gracie Mansion Register Mock-ups (Box 46, Folder 147)
    - Misc. Oversize
      - Inventing Memory – Erica Jong (Box 46, Folder 148)
      - Animal Magnetism (Box 46, Folder 148)
      - The Crisis of Democracy (Box 46, Folder 148)
      - Laying Waste (Box 46, Folder 148)
      - Gracie Mansion Register (Box 46, Folder 148)
      - Missile Envy (Box 46, Folder 148)
      - Snakeskin Binding (Box 46, Folder 148)
      - Birds of North America (Box 46, Folder 148)
      - The Star Book (Box 46, Folder 148)
      - Minsky in London Camberwell Essay (Box 46, Folder 148)
      - Long Island Guest Book (Box 46, Folder 148)
      - Dante's Inferno covers (Box 51)
      - The Bride's Treasure Chest (Box 53)
      - Minsky in London Printing Plates (Box 54, Folder 149)
  - From Series I: Biographical, circa 1970-1980s 1990
    - Book Arts in the USA Conference poster (Folder 1, Folder 150)
  - From Series IV: Project Files, 1980 1989
    - Minsky in London poster (Folder 1, Folder 150)
    - Book for Chairman of Brooklyn Museum (Folder 1, Folder 151)
    - Brooklyn Museum Director's Guestbook (Folder 1, Folder 151)
- 2011 Addition, 1994-2011
  2011 Addition (Boxes 58-61) are closed for processing and require curatorial permission before use.
  Preliminary box listing only.
  - Correspondence, 2010-2011 (Box 58)
  - Files on Freedom of Choice, 2010 (Box 58)
  - Files on Art of American Book Covers, Braziller, 2010 (Box 58)
  - Files on Material Meets Metaphor catalog, 2010; 1 of 3 (Box 58)
  - Lecture at Yale University Library, Fall 2010 and exhibition reception, 2 (Box 58)
  - Materials from SUNY/Purchase Experimental Book Course Fall, 2010 (Box 58)
  - Warner Music Group keepsake 1994 (Box 59)
  - Trial cover designs for American Decorated Publishers' Bindings (Box 59)
  - Files, proofs, etc. for Art of American Book Covers, Braziller 2010 (Box 59)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 59)
  - Files on Self-Portrait 2010 (Box 59)
  - Book art ephemera (Box 59)
  - Files, proofs, correspondence, manuscripts, etc. of Book Art of Richard Minsky, Braziller 2011 (Box 59)
  - Minsky promotional flyers (Box 59)
  - Conference ephemera (Box 59)
  - Fine Books & Collections with Minsky's column (Box 59)
  - Dummy for Book Art of Richard Minsky, including slip case for limited edition (Box 60)
  - Rejected proof for Franklin quote print for limited edition version of Book Art of Richard Minsky (Box 60)
  - Barnes & Noble 2010 Desk Calendar (Box 60)
  - Molds and hardware for Chateau Verlaines project (Box 61)
    See also Series V for Minsky's discussion of the wax molds for Minsky in Bed.
- 2012 Addition(s), 1971-2012
  2012 Addition (Boxes 62-70) are closed for processing and require curatorial permission before use.
  - The Second Exhibition of American Decorated Publisher's Bindings 1827-1929, 2003 (Box 62)
  - Pop Delusions – Exhibition announcements, 2012 (Box 62)
  - Barnes & Noble Events: The Book Art of Richard Minsky – Discussion and Signing (Box 62)
  - Unidentified material (Box 62)
  - The Artist and the Book – Today, slide show and talk (Box 62)
  - The Morgan Register (Box 62)
  - The Indian's Book (Box 62)
  - The Morgan Register (maquette for grid & steel cut with wrong dimensions) (Box 62)
  - CBA Minutes of the Meeting "Board of Directors", 1980-1997 (Box 63)
  - CBA Exhibition Catalogs, 1982-1989 (Box 63)
  - CBA Exhibition Catalogs, 1992-1999 (Box 63)
  - CBA/Exhibitions, 1986-1987 (Box 63)
  - CBA First Decade Exhibition at New York Public Library catalog, 1984; 2 (Box 63)
  - Book and Conference "Women of Color", 1986 (Box 63)
  - CBA – Fund Raising Project, 1986 (Box 63)
  - CBA Book Arts Review, 1984-1998; 2 (Box 63)
  - Geometry and New Math Exhibition (Books about Sex), 1996 (Box 63)
  - CBA Financial and budget papers, 1991-2004 (Box 63)
  - CBA Financial and budget papers, 2000-2004; 2 (Box 63)
  - "Love in a Life" by Robert Browning, 1994 (Box 63)
  - CBA documents, 1984-1992; 2 (Box 63)
  - CBA Workshops and Class schedules, 1980-2000 (Box 63)
  - CBA Classes, Events and Exhibitions catalogs, 2003-2004 (Box 63)
  - CBA Classes, Events and Exhibitions catalogs, 2003-2010 (Box 63)
  - CBA Napkins, 2005 (Box 63)
  - CBA Exhibition, 2005 (Box 63)
  - CBA Board Meeting, 2006-2007 (Box 63)
  - CBA Mission (Box 63)
  - CBA Miscellaneous (Box 63)
  - Correspondence, 1978-1979; 2 (Box 64)
  - Correspondence, 1983-1985; 2 (Box 64)
  - Personal Correspondence (Christmas cards, letters, postcards and greeting notes), 1984-1986; 2 (Box 64)
  - Personal Correspondence (Christmas cards, letters, postcards and greeting notes), 1985-1986 (Box 64)
  - Correspondence, 2004-2012 (Box 64)
  - Rory Golden's letters, 2004 (Box 64)
  - Brown University: "Walter Feldman's Book Arts Class", 2004-2005 (Box 64)
  - Personal and financial files (photos, cards, saving account books, etc.), 1969-1975 (Box 64)
  - North America Hand Papermaking, vols. 1 & 2, 1976 (Box 64)
  - National Council for Apprenticeship in Art and Craft (NCAAC), 1981-1984 (Box 64)
  - Rosalind Solomon – Film, Peru, 1981-1982 (Box 64)
  - Rosalind Solomon, 1981-1982 (Box 64)
  - Rosalind Solomon – India, 1982 (Box 64)
  - Rosalind Solomon, 1983-1986; 3 (Box 64)
  - Zacharias' Exhibition catalogs, 1983 (Box 64)
  - Personal and financial files (Bank statement, paid checks, deposit slips, Yankee season ticket and voter card), 1983-1986 (Box 64)
  - Bookworks by Tom Phillips – Catalogs, 1983 1986 (Box 64)
  - Life's Treasure Chests, INC. (LTC) By-Laws, 1984; 2 (Box 64)
  - Andrew Hoyem / Arion Press, 1984-1987 (Box 65)
  - Blue Mountain Center, 1985-1987 (Box 65)
  - Minnesota Center for Books Arts (MCBA), 1986-1987 (Box 65)
  - Getty Center Library (Invoices), 1987 (Box 65)
  - London Trip, May, 1987 (Box 65)
  - Craft International Board documents, 1987-1988 (Box 65)
  - Zabriskie Gallery, 1987-1988 (Box 65)
  - Other Exhibitions, 1987-1988 (Box 65)
  - Painted Bride Art Center, 1988 (Box 65)
  - The Lois de la Haba Agency, 1992 (Box 65)
  - Becoming Light, 1992 (Box 65)
  - John Simon Guggenheim Memorial Foundation: Fellowship application documents, 1988-1989 (Box 65)
  - John Simon Guggenheim Memorial Foundation: Fellowship application documents, 2005-2006 (Box 65)
  - Financial (Merrill Lynch EMA Signature Rewards program – Pop Delusions?), 2003 (Box 65)
  - Who's Who in the World, 2004-2006 (Box 65)
  - American Decorated Publisher's Binding 1875-1929, Catalog Subscription, 2004-2008 (Box 65)
  - The Artists' Book Conference, June 15-18, 2005, Wellesley College (Box 65)
  - University of Virginia – Documents, 2005 (Box 65)
  - Donald Bady – Box for Homer, 2005 (Box 65)
  - College Art Association (CAA): Membership information & ID cards, 2005-2013 (Box 65)
  - Chicago Center for Book & Paper, Jan. 27, 2006 (Box 65)
  - College Art Association (CAA) 94th Annual Conference information, Feb 22-25, 2006 (Box 65)
  - Ethics of Liberty- Proposal, 2006 (Box 65)
  - Ethics of Liberty, 2006 (Box 65)
  - University of Iowa Center for the Book Workshop, 2007 (Box 65)
  - Oak Knoll Fest XVI, Oct. 6th-7th, 2007 (Box 65)
  - Store lease and rental papers, 1974-1985 (Box 65)
  - Employment Agreement, 1983-1985 (Box 65)
  - Sonya Rapoport, Isomorphics, 1984 (Box 65)
  - Walter Askin, California State University, 1984 (Box 65)
  - Andre Kertesz (newspaper article), 1985 (Box 65)
  - Exhibitions – Rutgers, 1985 (Box 65)
  - Joni Mabe, 1985 (Box 65)
  - Income, 1985 (Box 65)
  - Metropolitan Museum of Art – Book Artchitecture Exhibition, 1985 (Box 65)
  - Travel documents, 1985 (Box 65)
  - Thomas Wenberg, 1986 (Box 65)
  - Dieu Donne Papermill Inc.: Fund for Paper, Print and the Book, 1988-1992; 4 (Box 65)
  - Dieu Donne Papermill Inc.: Fund for Paper, Print and the Book, 1993-1994 (Box 65)
  - Financial files, 1972-2001 (Box 65)
  - Financial files, 1986-2000 (Box 65)
  - Binding: Low Resolution proof sheets, 2000-2011 (Box 65)
  - Myra Donnelley, 1983-1984 (Box 65)
  - Legal documents, 1984 (Box 65)
  - Hard Candy, book cover (Box 65)
  - Arthur Ellis (Box 66)
  - Photographs -contact sheet (Box 66)
  - Photographs and negatives (Tango, etc.) (Box 66)
  - Stationery (Box 66)
  - Tools--Documents (Box 66)
  - Crystal Script (Box 66)
  - "For All Who Are Hungry" A Passover Haggadah (paper samples and CD) (Box 66)
  - Exhibition catalogs and book reviews, 1974-1987 (Box 66)
  - Exhibition catalogs and book reviews, 1988-2003 (Box 66)
  - Creative Arts Workshop (CAW) "Out of Bounds", 1975 (Box 66)
  - School of Visual Arts – Final Exam, 1977 (Box 66)
  - Life's Treasure Chest (LTC) Royalty Agreement, 1983 (Box 66)
  - Dante's Inferno, 1986 (Box 66)
  - Richard Minsky – Catalogs, 1992 (Box 66)
  - Pollock-Krasner Foundation, 1998 (Box 66)
  - Book conferences (Box 66)
  - Exhibition Announcements (Box 66)
  - Exhibitions – Reception Invitation cards, 1985-1986; 2 (Box 66)
  - Conferences – ID Badges (Box 66)
  - Book of Art of Richard Minsky (Book cover) (Box 66)
  - "Do It Yourself" proposal (Box 66)
  - Pop Delusions: Creation and Fabrication (Box 66)
  - First Ensemble for Tony Zwicker (Box 66)
  - Bill of Rights Exhibition (Box 66)
  - Photographs (Box 66)
  - Guest Book: Private Home, Long Island (photos and photocopies) (Box 66)
  - Book Art of Richard Minsky (Book cover) (Box 66)
  - Miscellaneous documents (Box 66)
  - Color transparencies from an unidentified project (Box 66)
  - Forbes magazine cover: A First Bound copy (Box 66)
  - The Golden Age of American Book Design – Barnes & Noble Desk Diary, 2013 (Box 66)
  - Planner Agendas, 1971-1979 (Box 66)
  - Planner Agendas, 1982-1983 (Box 66)
  - Planner Agendas, 1984 (Box 66)
  - Planner Agendas, 1985-1989 (Box 66)
  - Planner Agendas, 1990-1996 (Box 66)
  - Minsky Finances Incorporated, 1983 (Box 67)
  - Love and / or Terror- Book Exhibition, University of Arizona, 2003 (Box 67)
  - Rose Slivka (Box 67)
  - Newspaper articles (Box 67)
  - Correspondence, 1982-2003 (Box 67)
  - Book covers (photocopies), 2 (Box 67)
  - SLART, 2007-2008 (Box 68)
  - SLART, 2008-2009 (Box 69)
  - Minsky signature Stamping dies, 2004 2006 2007 2008 (Box 70)
  - Stamping dies: The Crisis of Democracy, The Book Cover Art of Thomas Watson Ball (first draft – not used) (Box 70)
  - The Esteban Vicente's 80th Birthday Box, 1982-1983 (Box 70)
  - Rock Magazine, 1983 and Comic book: Barbie, 1993, 1983 1993 (Box 70)
  - Ox Bow Workshop, 1985 (Box 70)
  - Exhibition announcements (Box 70)
  - Conference ID Badges (Box 70)
  - The Art of American Book Covers 1875-1930 (Box 70)
  - Teeth from The Geography of the Hunger (Box 62)
  - Samples of binding labels, 2000-2012 (Box 70)
  - Samples of binding labels, 2000-2012 (Box 62)
- 2013 Addition, 2012-2013
  2013 Addition (Boxes 70 & 62) are closed for processing and require curatorial permission before use.
  - American Decorated Publishers' Bindings, 1872-1929 (Box 70)
  - Pop Delusions: Creation & Fabrication – uncorrected proof, 2012 (Box 70)
  - The Book Cover Art of Thomas Watson Ball (proofs) (Box 70)
  - Bar Mitzvah? – brass die (Box 70)
  - Thomas Watson Ball – uncorrected proof, 2012 (Box 70)
  - Thomas Watson Ball –Deluxe uncorrected proof, 2012 (Box 70)
  - The Boston Globe, Saturday, May 4, 2013 (Box 62)
- 2014 Addition(s), 2003-2014
  2014 Additions (Boxes 44, 45, 71-74) are closed for processing and require curatorial permission before use.
  - Timothy Pida's paperwork, 2003-2005; 3 (Box 71)
  - Proofs of Holiday Card: Prophet Storms by Erica Jong (Box 71)
  - Bindery: Warner Music CD, 3 (Box 71)
  - Leather scraps (Timothy Pida), 4 (Box 71)
  - Branches (Box 71)
  - ARLIS – Conference Program Ad, 2014 (Box 71)
  - Freedom of Choice material (Box 71)
  - "CASING IN" with Richard Minsky – DVD, 2006; 1 DVD (Box 71)
  - Richard Minsky, Grolier Club, 2/22/2008 – Cassette, 1 audio cassette (Box 71)
  - Leather scraps (Timothy Pida), 3 (Box 71)
  - Jared Smith (Box 72)
  - The Right to Privacy (Box 72)
  - The Jungle Book (Bag) (Box 72)
  - Leather scraps (Timothy Pida) (Box 72)
  - Mary Ellen Mark – Prototypes "Unfamous", 5 (Box 73)
  - Mary Ellen Mark – Prototypes "Unfamous", 5 (Box 74)
  - Process materials – Leather binding/housing, 1 (Box 44)
  - Dale Guild Type Foundry announcement card, 1 (Box 45)
  - Print for "The Art of Living Well: A Celebration of Allan Stone's Life, February 5, 2007, The Morgan Library & Museum", 1 (Box 45)
  - 2 photographs of Allan Stone, 1 (Box 45)
  - "Prophet's Storm" New Year's card for Erica Jong and Ken Burrows, 2013; 1 (Box 45)
  - Musical Theory – manuscript by Richard Minsky, 2014; 1 (Box 45)
  - Unidentified print, 1 (Box 45)
  - Annotated, unbound manuscript for American Trade Bindings with Native American Themes, 1875-1933, 1 (Box 45)
  - Annotated, bound manuscript ("Incomplete Draft 2") for American Trade Bindings with Native American Themes, 1875-1933, 1 (Box 45)
  - Copy editor's notes [for American Trade Bindings with Native American Themes, 1875-1933?], 1 (Box 45)
  - Unbound signatures for American Trade Bindings with Native American Themes, 1875-1933, 1 (Box 45)
  - Large, unbound signatures for American Trade Bindings with Native American Themes, 1875-1933, 1 (Box 45)
  - Black-and-white copy of cover design by Margaret Armstrong for The Adventures of Captain Bonneville USA (1898), 1 (Box 45)
  - Letterpress proofs of title for American Trade Bindings with Native American Themes, 1875-1933, 1 (Box 45)
  - Process materials – Leather book cover for Breviary and scrap of marbled paper, 1 (Box 45)
  - Process materials – "The Morgan Register" stamped in red leather, 1 (Box 45)
  - Material Meets Metaphor: A Half Century of Book Art by Richard Minsky, 2010; 2 (Box 45)
  - Process materials – Printed book cloth fragment, 1 (Box 62)
  - Process materials – Print of The Morgan Register cover design, 1 (Box 62)